<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Using the USWDS Theme on Hugo USWDS</title><link>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/</link><description>Recent content in Using the USWDS Theme on Hugo USWDS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo Configuration</title><link>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/configuration-parameters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/configuration-parameters/</guid><description>Site-Wide Configuration Hugo provides a variety of configuration options. For simplicity, this documentation and associated examples assume a YAML-based, single file configuration is used for a site using this theme. In this case all Hugo site-wide configurations are made in the config.yaml located at the root of the website dirctory. Other options are available for configuring Hugo using alternate config file formats and directory structures, which are not covered on this page.</description></item><item><title>Page Templates</title><link>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/templates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/templates/</guid><description>Provided Templates This theme provides a set of default templates that support the basic types of pages needed by most websites.
These templates are highly configurable based on site-wide and page-specific configuration parameters. All templates share the ability to customize primary and secondary menus, side navigation, and other common features through these configuration parameters.
Use of these templates are described in the following subsections.
The Base Template Source baseof.html</description></item><item><title>Shortcodes</title><link>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/shortcodes/</guid><description> This theme provides the following Hugo shortcodes.
callout Shortcode imagemap Shortcode area Shortcode usa-alert Shortcode usa-graphic-list Shortcode usa-media-block Shortcode usa-grid-container Shortcode usa-grid-row Shortcode usa-grid-column Shortcode usa-hero Shortcode usa-intro Shortcode usa-section Shortcode usa-tag Shortcode usa-tagline Shortcode</description></item><item><title>Customizing CSS and JavaScript Resources</title><link>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/customizing-css-and-js/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nist.gov/hugo-uswds-docs/documentation/hugo/customizing-css-and-js/</guid><description>Customizing CSS Resources Sass Customizations Sass files are located in the themes assets/scss directory.
Site-Wide CSS Resources A CSS resource can be added to the site by placing the CSS file in the assets directory and then referencing this file using the custom_css site parameter in the config.yaml.
Page-Specific CSS Resources A CSS resource can be added to an individual page by placing the CSS file in the assets directory and then referencing this file using the custom_css page parameter in the page front matter.</description></item></channel></rss>